managementkits.com 2016-09-23

# Privacy Policy — Management Kits | Making management work

Management Innovation Services GmbH  
Management Kits Privacy Policy

Management Innovation Services GmbH provides via [www.managementkits.com](http://www.managementkits.com/) an individual or collaborative service to create, analyze, share, and discuss strategic business issues such management and organization topics (hereafter called "Content").

###  **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE PRACTICES**

 _Personal Data_

We collect personally identifiable information ("Personal Data") from you when you voluntarily choose to provide Personal Data. We use the Personal Data that we collect in order to provide and improve our services. Examples of Personal Data we collect include first name, last name, address, email address, telephone number, billing and credit card information, and information regarding your subscription.

 _Use of Personal Data_

Management Innovation Services GmbH uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data only in connection with the reason for which it was provided. When we receive your Personal Data from a Management Innovation Services GmbH Client with whom you have registered, we may use that Personal Data in order to contact you on behalf of that Management Innovation Services GmbH Client (via email or otherwise). Management Innovation Services GmbH and its affiliates also use your Personal Data and other non-personally-identifiable information collected through the Website to help us improve the content and functionality of the Website, to better understand the users of our Website, and to improve our services.

 _Aggregated Personal Data_

In an ongoing effort to better understand our users, we may analyze the Personal Data that is provided to the Website in aggregate form. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

 _Passively Collected Information_

When you interact with us through the Website, we receive and store certain additional non- personally-identifiable information. For example, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, browser type and language, referring/exit pages and URLs, other browser history, platform type, number of clicks, landing pages, cookie information, the pages you requested and viewed, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time. We only use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often users use parts of the Website or Services so that we can make the Website appealing to as many users as possible, and improve our Services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our users, collectively, use the Website. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and the Website, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience.

As an example: we use Google analytics to collect and review this information and to connect with Google Analytics Advertising Features. This allows us to better inform and target relevant groups. Currently we implemented:

-        Remarketing with Google Analytics  
-        Google Display Network Impression Reporting  
-        DoubleClick Platform integrations  
-        Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting

Information collected by Google analytics will be merged with your personal data only if we get your prior consent to do so.

Google analytics offers you to opt out of the data collection here. It is also possible to stop this data collection and information sending in your browsers settings.

### WE MAY SHARE PERSONAL DATA WITH:

 _Authorized service providers_

Our authorized service providers are companies that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, processing credit card payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analyses, supporting the Website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys or other features we offer. These service providers may have access to your Personal Data to the extent necessary to perform their functions, but we do not allow them to share or use any of your Personal Data for any other purpose.

 _Management Innovation Services GmbH affiliates_

We may share information we collect, including Personal Data, with Management Innovation Services GmbH-owned or affiliated businesses. Sharing information with our affiliates enables us to provide you with information about a variety of products and services that might interest you. All Management Innovation Services GmbH companies comply with applicable privacy and security laws and, at a minimum, in any commercial email they send to you, will give you the opportunity to choose not to receive such email messages in the future.

 _Protection of Management Innovation Services GmbH and others_

We may release Personal Data when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of our Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes, without limitation, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud monitoring, detection, and prevention.

We may release Personal Data in response to a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

### OTHER

When you use Management Innovation Services GmbH Services, you are subject to the Management Innovation Services GmbH Terms of Service.

Please see Management Innovation Services GmbH Support if you have questions about this service.

This page describes current Management Innovation Services GmbH practices with respect to this particular service. This information may change as Management Innovation Services GmbH revises this service by adding or removing features or using different service providers.
